Guide to Central Washington University Business and Financial Affairs 2019
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
Business and Financial Affairs Collection
1902-2016
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections 400 E University Way Ellensburg, WA 98926 (509) 963-1717 http://www.lib.cwu.edu/Archives-Special-Collections archives@cwu.edu
RG082-19-02
Central Washington University
37.5 cubic feet. 75 legal sized document boxes
Business Services exists to perform functions necessary to support the goals of Central Washington University. The services are twofold: those mandated by the external environment and those that provide specific services which directly support the goals of the University.
Historical Note
Central Washington University began as the Washington State Normal School in 1891. In 1937, the school was rechristened the Central Washington College of Education. In 1961, the school became Central Washington State College and, finally, in 1977, Central Washington University. This collection documents the financial affairs office of Central Washington University through the years of 1902 to 2016.
This collection includes maps, documents, and ledgers related to the business and financial affairs office of Central Washington University. The documents include committee meeting minutes, newspaper clippings, and documents showing the local community and campus over time.
Chronological
Open to the public for education research.
Documents transferred to Archives from Financial Affairs
Oversized documents in map drawer number one titled Welcome Center Feasibility Study, and CHCI remodel to ROTC, Date 2013
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Central Washington University Archives
Ellensburg, Washington
Education, Higher--Finance; Universities and colleges
City Planning; City and Town Life; Colleges and Universities; Public Finance; Washington
  - Invoices, Warrants, 1902-1911 (Box-folder 1-1)
  - Invoices, Warrants, 1909-1914 (Box-folder 1-2)
  - Invoices, Warrants, 1909-1915 (Box-folder 1-3)
  - Invoices, Warrants, 1912- (Box-folder 1-4)
  - Invoices, Art Supplies, 1913- (Box-folder 1-5)
  - Utility Invoices, Coal, 1909- (Box-folder 2-1)
  - Invoices, Hardware, Coal, 1909- (Box-folder 2-2)
  - Invoices, Subscriptions, 1910- (Box-folder 2-3)
  - Invoices, Lab Equipment, 1913- (Box-folder 2-4)
  - Invoices, Paper Supplies, 1914- (Box-folder 2-5)
  - Furniture, Class Supplies, 1904-1913 (Box-folder 3-1)
  - Supplies, 1910- (Box-folder 3-2)
  - Supplies, 1910-1914 (Box-folder 3-3)
  - Kindergarten, Supplies, 1911-1912 (Box-folder 3-4)
  - Requisitions, Department supplies, 1912-1916 (Box-folder 3-5)
  - Supplies, Furniture, 1913-1914 (Box-folder 4-1)
  - Requisitions, Department supplies, 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-2)
  - Requisitions, Department supplies, 1914- (Box-folder 4-3)
  - Class Supplies, 1915- (Box-folder 4-4)
  - Student Loan Applications, Committee, 1943-1948 (Box-folder 5-1)
  - Building Revenue Bonds, 1957-1992 (Box-folder 5-2)
  - Bond Sale Notice, 1958- (Box-folder 5-3)
  - Student Union Building Bond, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 5-4)
  - Series A,Tuition Bonds, 1966-1980 (Box-folder 5-5)
  - Series B, C, Tuition Bonds, 1968-1978 (Box-folder 5-6)
  - Schedule 1 Bonds, 1969- (Box-folder 5-7)
  - CWU Travel Regulations, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 5-8)
  - Reimbursement Schedules, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 5-9)
  - Voucher and Check Register, 1947- (Box-folder 6-1)
  - Voucher and Check Register, 1948- (Box-folder 6-2)
  - Voucher and Check Register, 1949- (Box-folder 6-3)
  - Revenue Bonds, 1956- (Box-folder 6-4)
  - Construction Accounts, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 6-5)
  - High Rise Dorms, Courson and Muzzall Halls, Schematics, Costs, 1966- (Box-folder 6-6)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 6-7)
  - Office of Financial Management, Correspondence, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 6-8)
  - Administrative Rules, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 6-9)
  - Accounting Staff, Meeting Minutes, 1984- (Box-folder 6-10)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1958-1970 (Box-folder 7-1)
  - Student Village Housing Bonds, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 7-2)
  - Student Union Bonds, 1969- (Box-folder 7-3)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 7-4)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 7-5)
  - Student Housing, Activities, Union, Revenue Bonds, 1976- (Box-folder 7-6)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 7-7)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 7-8)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1970- (Box-folder 8-1)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1975- (Box-folder 8-2)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1975- (Box-folder 8-3)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1980- (Box-folder 9-1)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1980- (Box-folder 9-2)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1980- (Box-folder 9-3)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1985- (Box-folder 10-1)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1980- (Box-folder 10-2)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1980- (Box-folder 10-3)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1985- (Box-folder 10-4)
  - Revenue Bonds, Account Statements, 1985- (Box-folder 10-5)
  - Travel, 1972-2003 (Box-folder 11-1)
  - Student Accounts, 1973-1987 (Box-folder 11-2)
  - Financial Aid, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 11-3)
  - Human Resources, 1999- (Box-folder 11-4)
  - Financial Management System, 2001- (Box-folder 11-5)
  - Financial Management System, Implementation, 2002- (Box-folder 11-6)
  - Financial Management System, Strategy, 2002- (Box-folder 11-7)
  - Student Administration System, 2002- (Box-folder 11-8)
  - Financial Management System, Reviews, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 11-9)
  - Budget Advisory Forum, 2003- (Box-folder 11-10)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, 2003- (Box-folder 11-11)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, 2004- (Box-folder 11-12)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, 2005- (Box-folder 11-13)
  - Capital and Operating Budget Open forum (Box-folder 11-14)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, 2004- (Box-folder 11-15)
  - Budget Planning, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 11-16)
  - Investments, 2006- (Box-folder 11-17)
  - Jones, Courtney Executive Files, 1984- (Box-folder 12-1)
  - Jones, Courtney Executive Files, 1986- (Box-folder 12-2)
  - Jones, Courtney Executive Files, 1987- (Box-folder 12-3)
  - Jones, Courtney Executive Files, 1989- (Box-folder 12-4)
  - Jones, Courtney Executive Files, 1991- (Box-folder 12-5)
  - Historic Budget Reduction, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 12-6)
  - Jones, Courtney Executive Files, 1992- (Box-folder 12-7)
  - Jones, Courtney Executive Files, 1993- (Box-folder 12-8)
  - Jones, Courtney Executive Files, 1994- (Box-folder 12-9)
  - Muzzall, Courson halls Topography, Campus Steam Utility Map, 1980-2004 (Box-folder 12-Oversize drawer)
  - Processing Grievances, 1986-1999 (Box-folder 13-1)
  - Cost of Attendance, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 13-2)
  - Capitalization Guidelines for fixed Assets, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 13-3)
  - Calendar Events, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 13-4)
  - Student Health and Counseling Center, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 13-5)
  - Units, Activities, 1997- (Box-folder 13-6)
  - Newsletter and Brochure, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 13-7)
  - Fire Risk Objectives, 1997-2004 (Box-folder 13-8)
  - Energy Services Proposal Lease Purchase, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 13-9)
  - Leases, Purchases, 1999- (Box-folder 13-10)
  - Financial Management System, Implementation, 2001- (Box-folder 13-11)
  - Observer, 2002- (Box-folder 13-12)
  - Parking Adjustment, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 13-13)
  - Purchase Card, 2004- (Box-folder 13-14)
  - M.E.C.H.A., Taco Bell, 2004- (Box-folder 13-15)
  - University Housing New Student Programs, 2004- (Box-folder 13-16)
  - Capital Budget Request, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 13-17)
  - Petty Cash Audits, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 13-18)
  - Student Health Insurance, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 13-19)
  - References, Tax Increase, 2005-2009 (Box-folder 13-20)
  - Student Financial Holds Data, 2008- (Box-folder 13-21)
  - Labor Management, Meeting Minutes, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 14-1)
  - Reorganization, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 14-2)
  - Corona, Rich Executive Files, 1993- (Box-folder 14-3)
  - Nasser, Abdul, Executive Files, 1997- (Box-folder 14-4)
  - Operating Budget Request, Capital Budget Request, Legislative Budget Request, Strategic Plan Instruction Packet, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 14-5)
  - Nasser, Abdul, Executive Files, 1998- (Box-folder 14-6)
  - Nasser, Abdul, Executive Files, 1998- (Box-folder 14-7)
  - Year 2000 Assessment, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 14-8)
  - Nasser, Abdul, Executive Files, 1999- (Box-folder 14-9)
  - Budget Overview, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 14-10)
  - Nasser, Abdul, Executive Files, 2001- (Box-folder 14-11)
  - Interim Report for Reaffirmation of Accreditation, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 15-1)
  - Final Interim Report for Accreditation, 1994- (Box-folder 15-2)
  - Strategic Plan, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 15-3)
  - Auxiliary Services Strategic Plan, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 15-4)
  - NASC Accreditation Steering Committee, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 15-5)
  - NASC Draft Report, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 15-6)
  - Report of Evaluation Committee from NWASC, 1979- (Box-folder 15-7)
  - Evaluation Committee Report NWASC, 1989- (Box-folder 15-8)
  - Executive Correspondence, 1969-1993 (Box-folder 16-1)
  - Council Meeting Minutes, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 16-2)
  - Jones, Courtney Executive Files, 1980- (Box-folder 16-3)
  - Jones, Courtney Executive Files, 1981- (Box-folder 16-4)
  - Jones, Courtney Executive Files, 1981- (Box-folder 16-5)
  - Jones, Courtney Executive Files, 1982- (Box-folder 16-6)
  - Jones, Courtney Executive Files, 1983- (Box-folder 16-7)
  - Diversity and Enrollment Planning, 1988-1994 (Box-folder 17-1)
  - SEPA Referral, 1993- (Box-folder 17-2)
  - Washington State Auditor, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 17-3)
  - Nasser, Abdul, Reader File, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 17-4)
  - Investigation of Alleged Misconduct in Auxiliary Services, 1994- (Box-folder 17-5)
  - Taco Bell, Analysis, 1995- (Box-folder 17-6)
  - Corona, Rich Reader File, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 17-7)
  - Business Affairs Development Council, Minutes, 1997- (Box-folder 17-8)
  - Enrollment Management Committee, 1997- (Box-folder 17-9)
  - Property Acquisition, Community Relations, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 17-10)
  - Reorganization, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 17-11)
  - Student Satisfaction, Westside Centers, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 17-12)
  - Student Affairs, 1996-2002 (Box-folder 18-1)
  - Attorney General, Correspondence, 1992-2010 (Box-folder 18-2)
  - Organizational Charts, 1995-2003 (Box-folder 18-3)
  - Public Safety and Police Services, Personnel Issues, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 18-4)
  - Space and Staffing Allocation Profile, 2005- (Box-folder 18-5)
  - State Auditor Report, 2006-2012 (Box-folder 18-6)
  - Cervantes Center, 2007- (Box-folder 18-7)
  - Testing and Assessment, 2007-2010 (Box-folder 18-8)
  - University Relations, 2008- (Box-folder 18-9)
  - House Appropriations Committee, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 18-10)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, Formal Complaints, 2009- (Box-folder 18-11)
  - Provost Council, 2009- (Box-folder 18-12)
  - Scholarship Advisory and Oversight Committee, 2009- (Box-folder 18-13)
  - M.I.S.T., HR, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 18-14)
  - Operating Budget Subcommittee, 2009-2011 (Box-folder 18-15)
  - Budget and Student Financial Services Organizational Chart, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 18-16)
  - Debt Book, 2011- (Box-folder 18-17)
  - Sport Club, Accounts, 2011- (Box-folder 18-18)
  - Base Budget Needs, 2000- (Box-folder 19-1)
  - Financial Model, 2003- (Box-folder 19-2)
  - B.A.R. Agenda, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 19-3)
  - Base Budget Needs, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 19-4)
  - Collective Bargaining, 2004- (Box-folder 19-5)
  - Internal Audit, 2004- (Box-folder 19-6)
  - Audit, Report, 2005- (Box-folder 19-7)
  - Budget Allocations, 2005- (Box-folder 19-8)
  - Audit Correspondence, 2005- (Box-folder 19-9)
  - Communication Challenges, 2006- (Box-folder 19-10)
  - Financial Aid Strategic Plan, 2006- (Box-folder 19-11)
  - Budget Presentation, 2007- (Box-folder 19-12)
  - Strategic Plans-HR, Academic Affairs, 2007- (Box-folder 19-13)
  - Policies, Contracts, 2008- (Box-folder 19-14)
  - Road Map Program Charter, 2008- (Box-folder 19-15)
  - Edmonds Center, 2002- (Box-folder 20-1)
  - State of the ASCWU, Address, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 20-2)
  - Naming Policy, 2003- (Box-folder 20-3)
  - Property Acquisitions, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 20-4)
  - President's Diversity Council, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 20-5)
  - Bachelor of Applied Science, 2004- (Box-folder 20-6)
  - Sexual Assault Policy, 2004- (Box-folder 20-7)
  - Washington Federation of State Employees Agreement, 2004- (Box-folder 20-8)
  - Guns on the College Campus, 2008- (Box-folder 20-9)
  - Capital Budgets Requests, 2009- (Box-folder 20-10)
  - University Residence Appliances, 2009- (Box-folder 20-11)
  - State Audit Report, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 20-12)
  - Helen McCabe park, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 20-13)
  - Moody's Investor Service, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 20-14)
  - Affirmative Action plan, 2010- (Box-folder 20-15)
  - Interagency Agreement, 2010- (Box-folder 20-16)
  - Institutional Effectiveness, 2010- (Box-folder 20-17)
  - Organizational Changes, 2010- (Box-folder 20-18)
  - Retirement Plan, 2010- (Box-folder 20-19)
  - System Revenue Bonds, 2010- (Box-folder 20-20)
  - University Committees and Councils, 2010- (Box-folder 20-21)
  - Council of Presidents, Teleconference, 2011- (Box-folder 20-22)
  - U.S. Bank Elavon Agreement, 2011- (Box-folder 20-23)
  - Financial Audit, 2013-2014 (Box-folder 20-24)
  - Budget Overview, 2014- (Box-folder 20-25)
  - Budget Restrictions, 2015- (Box-folder 20-26)
  - Board of Trustees, 2004- (Box-folder 21-1)
  - Archives, 2006- (Box-folder 21-2)
  - Distance Education, 2006- (Box-folder 21-3)
  - Employee Guidebook, 2006- (Box-folder 21-4)
  - Faculty Relations, 2006- (Box-folder 21-5)
  - Campus Security, Facilities, 2008- (Box-folder 21-6)
  - Cost Savings Salary, 2008- (Box-folder 21-7)
  - Demolition and Removal of Courson and Muzzall Halls, 2008- (Box-folder 21-8)
  - Department Space Profile, 2008- (Box-folder 21-9)
  - Equal Opportunity Grievance Committee, 2008- (Box-folder 21-10)
  - Minor Works Program, 2008- (Box-folder 21-11)
  - President's Correspondence, 2008- (Box-folder 21-12)
  - Squirrel Meeting, 2008- (Box-folder 21-13)
  - Information File, 1968-1978 (Box-folder 22-1)
  - Historical Data File, 1971-1994 (Box-folder 22-2)
  - IPEDS, Integrated Postsecondary Education Data System, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 22-3)
  - IPEDS, Integrated Postsecondary Education Data System, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 22-4)
  - Board of Trustees, Agenda, 2001- (Box-folder 22-5)
  - Washington Federation of State Employees Agreement, Ground Rules, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22-6)
  - Bargaining Agreement, Discussion, Notes, 2001- (Box-folder 22-7)
  - Collective Bargaining Unit 2, Discussion Notes, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22-8)
  - IPEDS, Integrated Postsecondary Education Data System, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22-9)
  - Bargaining Agreement, Correspondence, Public Employee, 2002- (Box-folder 22-10)
  - Budget Requests, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 23-1)
  - Employment Trends, 2003-2009 (Box-folder 23-2)
  - Spheres of Distinction, 2006- (Box-folder 23-3)
  - Budget Allocations, One-time Budget Enhancements, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 23-4)
  - Budget Base, Appropriations, 2006-2009 (Box-folder 23-5)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, Summer Budget, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 23-6)
  - Budget Requests, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 23-7)
  - Information Technology Services- Baseline Funding Base Budget, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 23-8)
  - Operating Budget, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 23-9)
  - Purchase Card Logs, 2008- (Box-folder 23-10)
  - Budget Allocations, 2008- (Box-folder 23-11)
  - Rich Corona's Retirement Party, 2008- (Box-folder 23-12)
  - Spheres of Distinction, 2008- (Box-folder 23-13)
  - Exempt Employee Schedule, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 23-13)
  - Salary Savings, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 23-14)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, 2009- (Box-folder 23-15)
  - Hiring/Travel Free, 2009- (Box-folder 23-16)
  - Earmark Issues, 2009- (Box-folder 23-17)
  - Summer Session Budget Proposal, 2009- (Box-folder 23-18)
  - Summer Session Budget Proposal, 2010- (Box-folder 23-19)
  - Annual Performance Evaluation, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 24-1)
  - Board of Trustees Report/Housing, Enrollment, 2005- (Box-folder 24-2)
  - Campus Facilities, Master Plan, 2005- (Box-folder 24-3)
  - Corona, Rich Correspondence, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 24-4)
  - Business and Service Contracts, 2006- (Box-folder 24-5)
  - Agreement with Big Bend Community College, 2009- (Box-folder 24-6)
  - Continuing Education, Revenue Distribution, 2009- (Box-folder 24-7)
  - Board of Trustees, 2009- (Box-folder 24-8)
  - Budget and Finance Committee, 2009- (Box-folder 24-9)
  - Capital Budget Subcommittee, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 24-10)
  - Dining, Residence Hall, 2009-2011 (Box-folder 24-11)
  - Budget Office, 2010- (Box-folder 24-12)
  - CWU Legal Services, 2010- (Box-folder 24-13)
  - Salary Savings, 2011- (Box-folder 24-14)
  - Auxiliary Budgets, Bond Schedule, 2011- (Box-folder 24-15)
  - Business Affairs Council, 2014- (Box-folder 24-16)
  - Foundation, Events, Celebration, 1990-2010 (Box-folder 25-1)
  - State Support for Higher Education, 1993-2009 (Box-folder 25-2)
  - Commercial Activities Committee, 1995-2009 (Box-folder 25-3)
  - Student Work Study, 1999-2009 (Box-folder 25-4)
  - Tuition Waiver Committee, 2003-2009 (Box-folder 25-5)
  - Auxiliary Services Departments Business Plan, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 25-6)
  - Retirement and Insurance Committee, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 25-7)
  - CWU Federal Credit Union, Minutes, 2006-2012 (Box-folder 25-8)
  - Athletics Loaner Cars, Foundation Matters, 2008- (Box-folder 25-9)
  - Positive Time Reporting, Compliance, 2008- (Box-folder 25-10)
  - Travel Justification, 2008- (Box-folder 25-11)
  - Auxiliaries and Revenue, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 25-12)
  - Procedure Review Committee Minutes, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 25-13)
  - Department Overviews: Human Resource, Financial Affairs, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 25-14)
  - Auxiliary services meeting, 2008-2010 (Box-folder 25-15)
  - Campus Art Wickiup, 2009- (Box-folder 25-16)
  - Sate of Auxiliaries Address H1N1 Contingency, 2009- (Box-folder 25-17)
  - Edu ventures Survey Results, Financial Aid Refund, 2009- (Box-folder 25-18)
  - Gladmar Park Committee, 2009- (Box-folder 25-19)
  - Government Relations/Legislative Blog, 2009- (Box-folder 25-20)
  - Impacts of Budget Cuts Due to Recession, 2009- (Box-folder 25-21)
  - Mini-Stats, 2009- (Box-folder 25-22)
  - CWU financial Report, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 25-23)
  - Financial Account Policy, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 25-24)
  - Budget and Finance Committee, 2010- (Box-folder 25-25)
  - Governor's Budget, 2010- (Box-folder 25-26)
  - Volunteer Retirement Incentive, 2010- (Box-folder 25-27)
  - Athletics Scholarship Fund, Camps, Clinics, 1970-2003 (Box-folder 26-1)
  - Student Organizations, Activities, 1974-1993 (Box-folder 26-2)
  - Motor-Pool, 1980-2005 (Box-folder 26-3)
  - IMC Instructional Media Center, 1982-1997 (Box-folder 26-4)
  - Student Employee Social Security, 1983-1991 (Box-folder 26-5)
  - AFROTC Uniform Commutation, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 26-6)
  - Employee Payroll, Overtime, 1987-1999 (Box-folder 26-7)
  - Student Financial Accounts, 1987-2003 (Box-folder 26-8)
  - Parking Plan, 1988- (Box-folder 26-9)
  - Department Purchases From university Store, 1989- (Box-folder 26-10)
  - Student Account Holds, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 26-11)
  - Continuing Education, 1992- (Box-folder 26-12)
  - President's Contract Compensation, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 26-13)
  - Equal Opportunity Employer, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 26-14)
  - Taylor, James Grievance, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 26-15)
  - Professional Studies, 1994- (Box-folder 26-16)
  - Retired and Senior Volunteer Program, 1994- (Box-folder 26-17)
  - Debt Policy, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 26-18)
  - International Programs Studies, Fees, 1996- (Box-folder 26-19)
  - CWU Theater Department and Mid Valley Performance Arts, Debt Collection, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 26-20)
  - Federal Student Aid, FIASP, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 26-21)
  - Capitalization Guidelines for Fixed Assets, 1991- (Box-folder 26-22)
  - Personnel Issues, Benefits, 1999-2006 (Box-folder 26-23)
  - Computer Recycling Program, 2010- (Box-folder 26-24)
  - Academic Planning Task Force, 2011- (Box-folder 26-25)
  - Campus Site and Development, 1969-1985 (Box-folder 27-1)
  - Ware Fair, Student Union Building Sale of Goods Policy, 1975-1990 (Box-folder 27-2)
  - Correspondence with City of Ellensburg, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 27-3)
  - Parking Committee, Campus Parking, 1976-1984 (Box-folder 27-4)
  - Labor Management Correspondence, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 27-5)
  - Garrity, Donald Newspaper Clippings, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 27-6)
  - Energy Advisory Board, 1982-1989 (Box-folder 27-7)
  - Facilities Planning Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 27-8)
  - V.P. Correspondence, 1983-1998 (Box-folder 27-9)
  - Physical Plant Correspondence, 1984- (Box-folder 27-10)
  - Insurance and Retirement Committee, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 27-11)
  - Business Manager Correspondence, Samuelson Building, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 28-1)
  - Property Acquisitions, Barkley, Tom, 1984-2006 (Box-folder 28-2)
  - Academic Plan, 1981- (Box-folder 28-3)
  - Labor Management Meeting Minutes, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 28-4)
  - Commercial Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 28-5)
  - Labor Management Correspondence, 1984- (Box-folder 28-6)
  - Labor Management Correspondence, 1985- (Box-folder 28-7)
  - Labor Management Correspondence, 1986- (Box-folder 28-8)
  - Labor Relations, Grievances, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 28-9)
  - Campus Site and Development, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 28-10)
  - Labor Management, Newspaper Clippings, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 28-11)
  - Commercial Activities, 1987- (Box-folder 28-12)
  - Commercial Reports, 1987- (Box-folder 28-13)
  - Labor Management Correspondence, 1987- (Box-folder 28-14)
  - Commercial Activities, Newspaper Clippings, 1987- (Box-folder 28-15)
  - A.C.E. Education Governor's Conference, 1988- (Box-folder 28-16)
  - Labor Management Correspondence, 1988- (Box-folder 28-17)
  - Enrollment Management Committee, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 28-18)
  - Information File, 1969- (Box-folder 29-1)
  - Faculty Activity and Workload Report, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 29-2)
  - Faculty Utilization by CWSC, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 29-3)
  - Information File, 1980- (Box-folder 29-4)
  - Information File, 1981- (Box-folder 29-5)
  - Information File, 1983- (Box-folder 29-6)
  - Information File, 1984- (Box-folder 29-7)
  - Fee Inventory, Initiative 960, 1978-2008 (Box-folder 29-8)
  - Fee Distribution, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 29-9)
  - Campus Police, Fire Arms, 1982-2004 (Box-folder 29-10)
  - Labor Management Correspondence, 1989- (Box-folder 29-11)
  - Campus Climate Report, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 29-12)
  - Campus Physical Environment Committee, 1997- (Box-folder 29-13)
  - Computer Labs Evaluation, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 29-14)
  - Unified Personnel System Committee, Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 30-1)
  - Strategic Plan, 1998- (Box-folder 30-2)
  - NACUB conference, Unfair Competition Bill, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 30-3)
  - Power Poles Re-Route, 1996- (Box-folder 30-4)
  - Power Poles Re-Route, Correspondence, 1996- (Box-folder 30-5)
  - V.P. Correspondence, 1999- (Box-folder 30-6)
  - V.P. Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 30-7)
  - Construction Projects, Meeting Notes, Newspaper Clippings, Reports, 2002- (Box-folder 30-8)
  - Bargaining Literature, Reports for Public Employees, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 30-9)
  - Interlocal Cooperative Agreement, 1995-2011 (Box-folder 31-1)